**The Project Gutenberg Etext of Moby Dick, by Herman Melville**
#3 in our series by Herman Melville

This work is still under construction, email me if you can help.

Copyright laws are changing all over the world, be sure to check
the copyright laws for your country before posting these files!!

Please take a look at the important information in this header.
We encourage you to keep this file on your own disk, keeping an
electronic path open for the next readers.  Do not remove this.


**Welcome To The World of Free Plain Vanilla Electronic Texts**

**Etexts Readable By Both Humans and By Computers, Since 1971**

*These Etexts Prepared By Hundreds of Volunteers and Donations*

Information on contacting Project Gutenberg to get Etexts, and
further information is included below.  We need your donations.


Title:  Moby Dick; or The Whale

Author:  Herman Melville

January, 2001  [Etext #2489]
[Date last updated: April 18, 2006]

**The Project Gutenberg Etext of Moby Dick, by Herman Melville**
*******This file should be named 2489.txt or 2489.zip*******

Project Gutenberg Etexts are usually created from multiple editions,
all of which are in the Public Domain in the United States, unless a
copyright notice is included.  Therefore, we usually do NOT keep any
of these books in compliance with any particular paper edition.

Caught and twisted--corkscrewed in the mazes of the line,
loose harpoons and lances, with all their bristling barbs and points,
came flashing and dripping up to the chocks in the bows of Ahab's boat.
Only one thing could be done.  Seizing the boat-knife, he critically
reached within--through--and then, without--the rays of steel;
dragged in the line beyond, passed it, inboard, to the bowsman,
and then, twice sundering the rope near the chocks--dropped the
intercepted fagot of steel into the sea; and was all fast again.

