ΔCENTRAL MISSOURI STATE UNIVERSITYΔManagement of Program Services- Coun 5130ΔAction
Research ProjectΔEvaluation GuideΔThree references citedΔ1Δ2Δ3Δ4Δ5ΔQuestions identified to
guide the research project Apollo. IncludesΔ1Δ2Δ3Δ4Δ5Δrationale of importance.ΔIdentifies
specific information to be collected, methods of collection and Δ1Δ2Δ3Δ4Δ5Δrelationship of data
to research questions.ΔIdentifies specific information analysis methods used in ApoΔllo. Includes
a rationale.Δ1Δ2Δ3Δ4Δ5Δ Professor Sand Identifies what decisions can be made based on
information analysis and how those decisions can be communicated with other populations in
the Sandford area (identify specifically).Δ1Δ2Δ3Δ4Δ5Δ