CENTRAL MISSOURI STATE UNIVERSITYஃManagement of Program Services- Coun 5130ஃAction
Research ProjectஃEvaluation GuideஃThree references citedஃ1ஃ2ஃ3ஃ4ஃ5ஃQuestions identified to
guide the research project Apollo. Includesஃ1ஃ2ஃ3ஃ4ஃ5ஃrationale of importance.ஃIdentifies
specific information to be collected, methods of collection and ஃ1ஃ2ஃ3ஃ4ஃ5ஃrelationship of data
to research questions.ஃIdentifies specific information analysis methods used in Apoஃllo. Includes
a rationale.ஃ1ஃ2ஃ3ஃ4ஃ5ஃ Professor Sand Identifies what decisions can be made based on
information analysis and how those decisions can be communicated with other populations in
the Sandford area (identify specifically).ஃ1ஃ2ஃ3ஃ4ஃ5ஃ